{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"11.8.0","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":1470,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":12,"width":970,"height":535,"responsive":false,"scalable":false,"launchFile":"index.html","isVRProject":false},"contentStructure":[{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_6","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["RMVUC"]},"constraints":{"length":5}}}},{"id":"SmartShape_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_2","title":"If the abandon code is “From Loc Empty (F)”, press the F3 key and type RMVUC in the “Trans ID” field to obtain the From and To locations. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_1","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_6","title":"Click the white box and type RMVUC. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_6","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide7911","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Entry_Box_6","SmartShape_2","Success_Shape_1","Hint_Shape_6","Failure_Shape_6"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide7911"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_3","title":"Enter the Workunit Status (ABN) in the “Workunit Status” field. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_4","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_5","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_7","title":"Enter the work unit status ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_8","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_8","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["ABN"]},"constraints":{"length":3}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_2","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_7","title":"Click the white box and type ABN. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_7","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide7944","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_3","SmartShape_4","SmartShape_5","Text_Caption_7","Text_Entry_Box_8","Success_Shape_2","Hint_Shape_7","Failure_Shape_7"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide7944"}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_9","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["24504798"]},"constraints":{"length":8}}}},{"id":"SmartShape_6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_6","title":"Enter the part number (24504798) in the “Product” field, then press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_3","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_8","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_8","title":"Click the white box and type 24504798 then press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_8","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_8","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8604","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Entry_Box_9","SmartShape_6","Success_Shape_3","Hint_Shape_8","Failure_Shape_8"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8604"}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_10","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_10","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["12609263"]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"SmartShape_10","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_10","title":"Write the From and To Locations and the quantity that was moved from RMVUC on the abandon log. Then, press F3. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_11","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_11","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_12","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_12","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_13","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_13","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_9","title":"Press the F3 key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide7977","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Entry_Box_10","SmartShape_10","SmartShape_11","SmartShape_12","SmartShape_13","Hint_Shape_9"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide7977"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_14","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_14","title":"To verify the quantity of the product in the From and To location, go to the physical location and type IPLMA in the “Trans ID” field. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_11","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_11","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["IPLMA"]},"constraints":{"length":5}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_4","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_10","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_10","title":"Click the white box and type IPLMA. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_9","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8037","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_14","Text_Entry_Box_11","Success_Shape_4","Hint_Shape_10","Failure_Shape_9"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8037"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_16","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_16","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_15","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_15","title":"To view the quantity of the product (24504798), press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_12","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_12","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["12609263"]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_11","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_11","title":"Press the Enter key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8070","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_16","SmartShape_15","Text_Entry_Box_12","Hint_Shape_11"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8070"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_18","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_18","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_20","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_20","title":"Verify the quantity in the From location matches the quantity in the IPLMA and document the quantity in the abandon log.  Then, press F3. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_13","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_13","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["12609263"]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_12","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_12","title":"Press the F3 key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8130","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_18","SmartShape_20","Text_Entry_Box_13","Hint_Shape_12"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8130"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_22","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_22","title":"To complete the abandon action, type RMVUC in the “Trans ID” field. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_14","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_14","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["RMVUC"]},"constraints":{"length":5}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_5","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_13","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_13","title":"Click the white box and type RMVUC. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_10","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_10","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8190","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_22","Text_Entry_Box_14","Success_Shape_5","Hint_Shape_13","Failure_Shape_10"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8190"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_23","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_23","title":"Enter the license plate number (72415464) in the “License Plate” field. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_15","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_15","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["72415464"]},"constraints":{"length":8}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_6","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_14","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_14","title":"Click the white box and type 72415464. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_11","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_11","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8250","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_23","Text_Entry_Box_15","Success_Shape_6","Hint_Shape_14","Failure_Shape_11"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8250"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_24","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_24","title":"To remove the part from the abandoned status, press the Tab key to navigate to the “Modify-dtl” screen. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_25","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_25","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_26","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_26","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_16","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_16","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["12609263"]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_15","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_15","title":"Press the Tab key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8283","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_24","SmartShape_25","SmartShape_26","Text_Entry_Box_16","Hint_Shape_15"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8283"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_27","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_27","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_28","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_28","title":"To resolve the abandoned workunit, press the R key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_17","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_17","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["R"]},"constraints":{"length":1}}}},{"id":"SmartShape_29","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_29","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_8","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_8","title":"ABN ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_32","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_32","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_7","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_16","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_16","title":"Click the white box and type R. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_12","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_12","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8346","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_27","SmartShape_28","Text_Entry_Box_17","SmartShape_29","Text_Caption_8","SmartShape_32","Success_Shape_7","Hint_Shape_16","Failure_Shape_12"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8346"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_30","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_30","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_31","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_31","title":"You have completed this process. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8406","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_30","SmartShape_31"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8406"}}},{"id":"Pool423","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":423,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"FromLocEmptyTraining","class":"project","title":"FromLocEmptyTraining","children":["Slide7911","Slide7944","Slide8604","Slide7977","Slide8037","Slide8070","Slide8130","Slide8190","Slide8250","Slide8283","Slide8346","Slide8406"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":379,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":true,"questions":[],"minScore":0,"maxScore":0,"passScore":0}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"enabled":false},"playbar":{"enabled":true,"cc":false,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":true,"rewind":true,"close":true,"mute":true,"progressBar":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"launch_content","SCCriteria":"launch_content","exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide7911","title":"Slide 1"},{"id":"Slide7944","title":"Slide 2"},{"id":"Slide8604","title":"Slide 3"},{"id":"Slide7977","title":"Slide 4"},{"id":"Slide8037","title":"Slide 5"},{"id":"Slide8070","title":"Slide 6"},{"id":"Slide8130","title":"Slide 7"},{"id":"Slide8190","title":"Slide 8"},{"id":"Slide8250","title":"Slide 9"},{"id":"Slide8283","title":"Slide 10"},{"id":"Slide8346","title":"Slide 11"},{"id":"Slide8406","title":"Slide 12"}]}